punchout2go.com 2019-05-03

# PunchOut2Go :: Privacy Policy

PunchOut2Go is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and data. Our Privacy Policy has been drafted to comply with applicable data privacy laws, in particular, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). If the GDPR does not apply to you, not all terms of this Privacy Policy may be relevant to you. To learn more about our approach to GDPR compliance, please click here.

PunchOut2Go complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. 

PunchOut2Go has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please [click here](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).   
 ****

Individuals have access to personal information about him/her that PunchOut2Go holds and is able to correct, amend, or delete that information where it is inaccurate, or has been processed in violation of the Principles, except where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the individual's privacy in the case in question, or where the rights of persons other than the individual would be violated.

PunchOut2Go offers individuals the opportunity to choose (opt out) whether their personal information is to be disclosed to a third party or to be used for a purpose that is materially different from the purpose for which it was originally collected. Individuals can opt out of receiving marketing materials by clicking the link "Unsubscribe" in any PunchOut2Go email.

PunchOut2Go takes responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. PunchOut2Go shall remain liable under the Principles if its agent processes such personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless PunchOut2Go proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

PunchOut2Go is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) and the possibility, under certain conditions, for the individual to invoke binding arbitration

PunchOut2Go is required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, and is liable in cases of onward transfers to third parties.

## What information do we collect?

PunchOut2Go may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website (including form data)
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including purchase credentials)
  * information about transactions carried out over this website
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services; and
  * any other information that you send to PunchOut2Go

## How do we use your information?

PunchOut2Go may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website
  * personalize the website for you
  * enable your access to and use of the website services (including PunchOut2Go PunchOut Catalog Gateway)
  * publish information about you on the website
  * send you products that you purchase
  * supply services that you purchase
  * send statements and invoices
  * collect payments from you
  * send you marketing communications

Where PunchOut2Go discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, PunchOut2Go may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

## Securing your data

PunchOut2Go will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of your personal information.

PunchOut2Go will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

## Cross-border data transfers

Information that PunchOut2Go collects may be stored, processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which PunchOut2Go operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

## Do we use "cookies"?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

## Updating this statement

PunchOut2Go may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

## Other websites

This website contains links to other websites. PunchOut2Go is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

## Dispute Resolution

Within the scope of this privacy notice, if a privacy complaint or dispute cannot be resolved through PunchOut2Go, LLC’s internal processes, PunchOut2Go, LLC has agreed to participate in the [VeraSafe Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure](https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/dispute-resolution/privacy-shield-dispute-procedure/). Subject to the terms of the VeraSafe Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure, VeraSafe will provide appropriate recourse free of charge to you. To file a complaint with VeraSafe under the Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure, please submit the required information to VeraSafe here: [https://www.verasafe.com/privacy- services/dispute-resolution/submit- dispute/](https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-%20services/dispute-resolution/submit-%20dispute/).

## Contact PunchOut2Go

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or PunchOut2Go's treatment of your personal information, please write:

  * by email to info@punchout2go.com
  * by mail to PunchOut2Go LLC, 3445 Seminole Trail #218, Charlottesville, Virginia 22911
